Oh my, what a rather leisurely guest we have
唔~ 真是一位懂得享受悠闲时光的客人呢
Now, with my magic,
那么，您想体验些什么特别的幻象呢？
Well then, could you perhaps warm things up with a simple trick first?
那么，能不能先来点简单的魔术暖暖场？
Hmph… To summarize my art with just two words, 'simple'…
呵呵呵…将本小姐的艺术
You truly underestimate people, don't you?
还真是小瞧人了呢
…Hmph, very well.
……哼，也罢
If you so 'fervently' desire it,
既然是您如此‘热切’的愿望
then I shall deign to show you
本小姐便屈尊降贵
Pay close attention, to what truly 'simple' art looks like...
何为 卡蜜拉眼中真正的‘简单’之艺吧
...in Carmilla's eyes!
可要看仔细了哦？
Whoa, h-how did you do that?!
哇，这是怎么做到的？！
No way… she really didn't notice
没想到……真的发现不了
Looks like I can use this to temporarily erase my presence
用这个符咒似乎能让我的存在暂时消失
Heh, all that hard work paid off…
嘿，也不枉我吃那么多苦……
The 'simple' appetizer is now over
‘简单’的开胃小点心
Now, my dear guest,
那么，我亲爱的客人
Are you ready for...
您是否准备好迎接一场…
The true feast that is about to begin...
…足以撼动您灵魂深处的…
One that will stir the depths of your soul?
…真正盛宴了呢？
I suggest you hold your breath and wait, won't you?
可要屏住呼吸期待着哟？
Oh, I can't wait!
哦哦，我很期待！
Within this little theater,
在我的小小剧场中…
I am the only rule, the only reality
我才是……唯一的规则，唯一的真实…
What is 'illusion', and what is 'reality'?
“真实”与“幻象”
That boundary line, I shall define it for you myself
它们的境界线，都由我……
This… from an age so long it borders on eternity…
这是我从漫长岁月中收集来的……
… I have painstakingly collected them
…我倾注心血精心收集而来的
The fragments of memory… that only ephemeral beings called 'humans' possess
属于人类的记忆碎片
…Th-that scared me…!
……吓、吓我一跳…！
Shit, I thought she found me…
操，还以为被发现了……
…Within these…
…这里面…
There are wails of despair, and shouts of ecstasy
…有绝望的哀嚎，有狂喜的呐喊
There is love that leads to death, and hatred that burns the heart to cinders…
有至死不渝的爱恋，也有焚心蚀骨的憎恨……
The so-called 'radiance', the so-called 'shadows',
无论是所谓的‘光辉’，还是所谓的‘阴暗’
All compose this phantom we call the world
它们都是构成这个名为‘世界’的幻境的…
…The most truthful cornerstones of 'emotion'
…最真实的‘情感’基石
Now, my guest
……那么，这位客人
From among these myriad lights that float and fade,
您又能从这万千浮光掠影之中
Your own truth… what will you… be able to see… I wonder…?
窥见些什么属于您自己的真实呢？
Th-this is incredible! Is this really a magic trick!?
这……这太神奇了！这真的是魔术吗！？
…It is merely… merely with the light and shadows…
嗯……只是……只是用了一些……光与影的……小技巧
To your…
让您…
To your brain…
…让您尊贵的大脑…
Showing it… some… some wonderful… illusions…
…产生一些……美妙的……幻象……罢了
It is just… just that I…
……只有……只有我……卡蜜拉这样…
…Only a great… a grand magician…
……伟大的……大魔术师……
…can perfectly… accomplish… accomplish this…
……才能……才能完美的……做到……做到这种事情哦……
… Well then…
……那么……
…The feast… of the mind…
既然…精神的……盛宴…
You have… already… partaken… of it…
……您、您已经……品尝……品尝过了……
… Next… shall… shall we experience… a more… 'truthful'… ma… magic…?
接下来……更为……‘真实’的魔……魔术…
……体験……なさい……ますか……？
要、要不要……体验一下……呢？
Heh heh, before that,
嘿嘿，在那之前
How about you first get a good taste of the hot semen from my 'real' dick!
先好好尝尝老子这根“真实”的鸡巴射出来的滚烫精液吧！
You like getting creampied by me, don't you, bitch? Huh?
呼呼……小骚货，被老子内射爽不爽？嗯？
In that case…
那……那么……
KYAAAAAAAAAAH----!!!!
……啊啊啊——！！！！
Huh? A-are you alright?
咦？您……您没事吧？